localiiz.com 2014-05-15

# Privacy Policy

**1\. Introduction**

We at Localiiz take the private nature of your personal information very seriously. It's our goal to bring you information that's relevant and targeted to your individual needs but we also protect your privacy at the same time. The following policy describes how we treat the information we collect from you whenever you visit our website, enter or register for any competition or giveaway and/or subscribe for or receive our emails, pulsits, newsletters or other communications. 

Welcome to our website, [www.localiiz.com](http://www.localiiz.com/) ("Localiiz.com" or the "site"). This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Localiiz.com (HK) Limited collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from you and from other users of Localiiz.com. If you continue to browse and use Localiiz.com, you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by this Privacy Policy which, together with our Terms of Use, govern Localiiz.com (HK) Limited's relationship with you in relation to Localiiz.com. If you disagree with any part of this Privacy Policy, please do not use Localiiz.com. 

**2\. Definitions**

"Localiiz.com", "Localiiz" or the "site" refers to our website, www.localiiz.com. The term Localiiz.com (HK) Limited or "us" or "we" refers to the owner of Localiiz.com. We are a company incorporated in Hong Kong with registration number 1553324. The term "you" or "User" refers to the user or viewer of Localiiz.com. 

**3\. Acceptance of Terms of Use**

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Localiiz.com and Localiiz.com (HK) Limited collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from you and from other users of Localiiz.com. If you continue to browse and use Localiiz.com, you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by this Privacy Policy which, together with our Terms of Use, govern Localiiz.com and Localiiz.com (HK) Limited’s relationship with you in relation to Localiiz.com. If you disagree with any part of this Privacy Policy, please do not use Localiiz.com. 

This Privacy Policy is subject to change by us at any time in our discretion. Your use of Localiiz.com after such changes are implemented constitutes your acknowledgement and acceptance of the changes. Please consult this Privacy Policy regularly. 

**4\. Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Localiiz.com. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, phone number. Users may, however, visit Localiiz.com anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain site related activities. 

**5\. Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with Localiiz.com. Non-personal identification information may include age, annual income, buying preferences, browser name, type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to Localiiz.com, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. We may use this data to improve our site and/or personalize your experience on our website in order to bring you more targeted and relevant content and to display such content according to your preferences. We may share this information with others, such as advertisers interested in advertising on our website, though not on an individual basis. 

**6\. Web browser cookies**

Localiiz.com may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. 

**7\. How we use collected information**

Localiiz.com (Hong Kong) Limited collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes: 

(i) to analyze and share in an aggregate, anonymous form (which will not contain any personally identifiable information about you) for our business purposes – for example, to enable us to understand how our Users as a group use the site, services and resources provided on Localiiz.com, such as how much time our Users spend on our site and which other websites Users come from before, and go to after, visiting our website, and to analyse User usage trends. The collection of this information allows us to, among other things, personalize user experience, prepare for traffic load demands, manage our content, efficiently disseminate our pulsits, newsletters and other communications, and seek compatible advertisers and partners; 

(ii) to improve Localiiz.com - we continually strive to improve our website, emails, pulsits, newsletters and other communications and offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you; 

(iii) to improve customer service - your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs; 

(iv) to administer a content, promotion, survey or other site feature - to send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them; 

(v) to send periodic emails, pulsits, newsletters and other communications – if a User decides to become a member of Localiiz.com or to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails, pulsits, newsletters and other communications that may include articles, company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, pulsits, newsletters and other communications, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions within each email, pulsit, newsletter or other communication or the User may contact us at [hello@localiiz.com](mailto:hello@localiiz.com). 

**8\. How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on Localiiz.com. 

Sensitive and private data exchange between Localiiz.com and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. 

**9\. Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. 

**10\. Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on Localiiz.com that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. Any links from Localiiz.com to other website are provided for your convenience to provide further information. We do not endorse, and are not responsible for, the content of any of those third-party websites. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from Localiiz.com. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to Localiiz.com, is subject to that website's own terms and policies. 

**11\. Advertising**

Ads appearing on Localiiz.com may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

**12\. Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Localiiz.com (HK) Limited has the discretion to update this Privacy Policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the Privacy Policy page of Localiiz.com, and revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy periodically and become aware of modifications. 

**13\. Governing Law**

You agree that your use of Localiiz.com, this Privacy Policy and any disputes relating thereto shall be governed in all respects by the laws of the Hong Kong. Any dispute relating to this Privacy Policy shall be resolved solely in courts of Hong Kong. 

**14\. Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of Localiiz.com or your dealings with Localiiz.com, please contact us at: 

Localiiz.com (HK) Limited  
3/F, 6 Tank Lane  
Sheung Wan  
Hong Kong 

+852 2559 5626 

Thank you for visiting Localiiz.com. 

Last updated on 1 September 2013
